FIDELIS ONUORAH NWABISI

Nsugbe Anambra | fidelisnwabisi@gmail.com | 08094163527 & 08119738965

PROFILE

Ability to work efficiently under pressure. Creative and analytical. Leadership, organizational and presentation skills. Reliable Employee & Engagement Officer with energetic and resourceful customer service professional, Human Resource Personnel and Project Manager with over four years of experience resolving customer complaints, managing projects and promoting conflict resolution. Ability to cultivate key client relationships for multiple campaigns in diverse industries. Expertise in client services, account management and relationship-building.

BIO DATA

Date of Birth - 8th June, 1994

Sex - Male
Marital Status - Single
Town - Nsugbe

Local Government Area - Anambra East
State - Anambra
Nationality - Nigerian

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

- Project Management
- Customer Relationship Managemernt
- Human Resource Management
- Health Safety and Environment Managemernt
- Excellent organisational skills
- Highly Proficient in Computer Applications; (AI, Corel Draw, MS: Word, PowerPoint, Excel and Google Apps, Mobile Application Development)
- Management skills
- Team Player
- Communication skills
- Leadership skills
- Good Problem Solving Skills
- Stakeholder Management
- Writing Skills: Written articles on leadership and social issues, concept notes and proposals and Curriculum Design
- Strength: Data Analysis, Programme Implementation, Training and Facilitation
- Interest: Education, Employability, Youth Transition and Research

CERTIFICATION AND TRAINING

OSHAcademy Human Resource Management.	2022
OSHAcademy Project Management Professional	2022
OSHAcademy Customer Care Relationship Management.	2022
OSHAcademy Health Safety and Environment Training (HSE 1 & 2)	2022
OSHAcademy Ocupational Safety and Health Training (HSE 3)	2022
National Youth Service Corps Discharge Cetificate	2022

EDUCATION

First School Leaving Certificate

2005

Credit Level

Trinity Primary School Onitsha

(2000 - 2005)

West African Senior Secondary School Certificate Examination (WASSCE)

Christ the King College Onitsha

2011 (2005 – 2011)

Nigeria Certificate on Education (NCE)

2014

2019

Credit

Nwafor Orizu College of Education, Nsugbe

(2011 - 2014)

Bachelor's Degree in Education Religion (B.Ed.)

• 2:1, Second Class Honours, Upper Division

University of Nigeria Nsukka

(2014 - 2019)

WORK HISTORY

Tonie Osegbo's Blog

2016 - PRESENT

Social Media Content Manager

Tribe Technology Accelerator

April 2018 - April 2019

Position: Sales Representative

- Promptly respond to customer enquiries in person or via phone, email, mail or social media.
- Quickly and efficiently open customer accounts by accurately recording account information.
- Maintain financial accounts by processing customer adjustments in a professional manner.
- Increased customer base by 30% during the year 2018 due to the delivery of quick service.

Igbo Proverbs May 2019 - May 2020

- Social Media Content Manager
- Web Developer (<u>www.igboproverbs.com</u>)
- Online Book Publisher on Okadabooks and Amazon

Udemy Naija 2019 - PRESENT

• Web Developer (<u>www.udemynaija.com</u>)

College of Education, Warri

April 2021 – February 2022

- Worked under Academics Office and as a Data Entry Officer
- P.A to the Secretary Academic Board of College of Education, Warri

Policy Africa August 2021 – PRESENT

- Content Creator
- Web Developer and Manager (www.policyafrica.com.ng)

Fire Centre Church September 2022 – PRESENT

Virtual Assistant for the Church

Research Bank March 2022 – PRESENT

- Web Deveoper for (<u>www.researchbak.com.ng</u>)
- Website Manager

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

AIESEC (Enugu in Nsugbe) - Non-Profit Organization

June 2012 - August 2017

: Delegate at National Training Seminar by AIESEC Nigeria at Oshogbo: 2012.

- AIESEC Enugu in Nsugbe Information Management, Communication and Promotions Team Leader:
- 2012-2014.
- Organizing Committee Team Member Information Management, Communication and Promotions in
- AIESEC Enugu Recruitment at Nsukka and Nsugbe: 2013.
- Organizing Committee Team Leader Information Management, Communication, and Promotions in
- . AIESEC Enugu Local Training Seminar at Nsugbe: 2013.
- AIESEC Enugu in Nsugbe Team Leader Outgoing Exchange: 2014-2015.
- : Delegate at AIESEC Enugu Local Training Seminar 2015 at Calabar.
- Expansion Manager AIESEC Enugu in Nsugbe: 2016-2017.

Book Alive Initiative - Non-Profit Organization

June 2015 - PRESENT

- Web Developer and Manger (www.bai.com.ng)
- Logistics Manager

Student Union Government of Nwafor Orizu College of Education

2016

Production Manager for the SUG Light Magazine

Nigerian Federation of Catholic Students of Nwafor Orizu College of Education

2016

Federation Week cum Cultural Fiesta ICT and technical manager Manage

AngusHub - Youth Mentoring Organization

2016 - PRESENT

- Content Manager
- Developing Entrepreneurs Conference Manager, February 2018

National Association of Computer Science Students, NOCEN

2017

Media Team Lead for the ICT in Diversity Conference

Google Developers Group Aba - Youth Mentoring Organization

2017

Delegate at Google Developers Group DevFest Southern and Eastern Nigeria

TechTiary - Youth Mentoring Organization

2017

Delegate at TechTiary Forum at Lagos

Tori Africa (Formerly Campus Tori) - Youth Mentoring Organization

2017

Sales team leader at Transformers conference Nsugbe

StartUp Anambra - Youth Mentoring Organization

December 2018 - PRESENT

- Media Team
- Social Media Content Manager

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS

- Rotary International Certificate of Membership by Rotaract Club of NOCEN, District 9140 (26th of June, 2012)
- Teachers Registration Council of Nigeria (March 2020 PRESENT)

REFEREE

Dr. Mrs. Rosemary Akwobi

Principal Lecturer, Home Economics Department, Nwafor Orizu College of Education, Nsugbe maryanneakwobi@gmail.com 08131399414